{
	"config": [
		{
			"lang": "EN",
			"rotate": "Rotate",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Move",				

			"colors": "Colors",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Explore Product in 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Return to 3D View",
			"howToUseMenu": "How to use",
			"mainmenu": "Main Menu",

			"previousView": "Previous View",
			"nextView": "Next View",
			"resetView": "Reset View",

           	"previous": "Previous",
			"next": "Next",
			"reset": "Reset",			

			"animations": "Reduce Transitions",
			"onScreenControls": "On-Screen Controls",

			"productview": "Product View",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Front",
			"back": "Back",
			"left": "Left",
			"right": "Right",
			"bottom": "Bottom",
			"top": "Top",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},

		{
			"lang": "DA",
			"rotate": "Roter",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Flyt",					

			"colors": "Farver",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Se produktet i 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Vend tilbage til 3D-visning",
			"howToUseMenu": "Brugsvejledning",
			"mainmenu": "Hovedmenu",

			"previousView": "Forrige visning",
			"nextView": "Næste visning",
			"resetView": "Nulstil visning",

            "previous": "Forrige",
			"next": "Næste",
			"reset": "Nulstil",

			"animations": "Reducer overgange",
			"onScreenControls": "Kontrolelementer på skærmen",

			"productview": "Produktvisning",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Forside",
			"back": "Tilbage",
			"left": "Venstre",
			"right": "Højre",
			"bottom": "Bund",
			"top": "Top",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "DE",
			"rotate": "Drehen",
			"zoom": "Zoomen",
			"move": "Bewegen",						

			"colors": "Farben",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Produkt in 3D erkunden",
			"returnTo3dView": "Zurück zur 3D-Ansicht",
			"howToUseMenu": "Verwendung",
			"mainmenu": "Hauptmenü",

			"previousView": "Vorherige Ansicht",
			"nextView": "Nächste Ansicht",
			"resetView": "Ansicht zurücksetzen",

            "previous": "Zurück",
			"next": "Weiter",
			"reset": "Zurücksetzen",

			"animations": "Übergänge vermindern",
			"onScreenControls": "On-Screen-Steuerelemente",

			"productview": "Produktansicht",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Vorderseite",
			"back": "Hinten",
			"left": "Links",
			"right": "Rechts",
			"bottom": "Unten",
			"top": "Oben",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},

		{
			"lang": "ES",
			"rotate": "Girar",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Movimiento",						

			"colors": "Colores",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Explorar producto en 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Volver a la vista 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Cómo utilizar",
			"mainmenu": "Menú principal",

			"previousView": "Vista anterior",
			"nextView": "Vista siguiente",
			"resetView": "Restablecer vista",

            "previous": "Anterior",
			"next": "Siguiente",
			"reset": "Restablecer",

			"animations": "Reducir transiciones",
			"onScreenControls": "Controles en pantalla",

			"productview": "Vista del producto",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Parte frontal",
			"back": "Volver",
			"left": "Izquierda",
			"right": "Derecha",
			"bottom": "Parte inferior",
			"top": "Parte superior",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},

		{
			"lang": "FR",
			"rotate": "Faire pivoter",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Déplacer",						

			"colors": "Couleurs",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Explorer le produit en 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Revenir à la vue 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Utilisation",
			"mainmenu": "Menu principal",

			"previousView": "Vue précédente",
			"nextView": "Vue suivante",
			"resetView": "Réinitialiser la vue",

            "previous": "Précédent",
			"next": "Suivant",
			"reset": "Réinitialiser",

			"animations": "Réduire les transitions",
			"onScreenControls": "Commandes à l’écran",

			"productview": "Vue du produit",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Avant",
			"back": "Retour",
			"left": "Gauche",
			"right": "Droite",
			"bottom": "Bas",
			"top": "Haut",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"			
		},
		{
			"lang": "FR-CA",
			"rotate": "Faire pivoter",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Déplacer",						

			"colors": "Couleurs",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Explorer le produit en 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Retourner à l’affichage 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Utilisation",
			"mainmenu": "Menu principal",

			"previousView": "Affichage précédent",
			"nextView": "Affichage suivant",
			"resetView": "Réinitialiser l’affichage",

            "previous": "Précédent",
			"next": "Suivant",
			"reset": "Réinitialiser",

			"animations": "Réduire les transitions",
			"onScreenControls": "Commandes à l’écran",

			"productview": "Affichage du produit",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Avant",
			"back": "Précédent",
			"left": "Gauche",
			"right": "Droite",
			"bottom": "Bas",
			"top": "Haut",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},

		{
			"lang": "IT",
			"rotate": "Rotazione",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Spostamento",						

			"colors": "Colori",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Scopri il prodotto in 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Torna alla vista 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Modalità di utilizzo",
			"mainmenu": "Menu principale",

			"previousView": "Vista precedente",
			"nextView": "Vista successiva",
			"resetView": "Reimposta vista",

            "previous": "Indietro",
			"next": "Avanti",
			"reset": "Reimposta",

			"animations": "Riduci transizioni",
			"onScreenControls": "Comandi a schermo",

			"productview": "Vista prodotto",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Parte anteriore",
			"back": "Indietro",
			"left": "Lato sinistro",
			"right": "Lato destro",
			"bottom": "Parte inferiore",
			"top": "Parte superiore",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "JA",
			"rotate": "回転",
			"zoom": "拡大・縮小",
			"move": "移動",						

			"colors": "カラー",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "3Dで製品を詳しく見る",
			"returnTo3dView": "3Dビューに戻る",
			"howToUseMenu": "使用方法",
			"mainmenu": "メイン メニュー",

			"previousView": "前の表示",
			"nextView": "次の表示",
			"resetView": "表示のリセット",

            "previous": "前へ",
			"next": "次へ",
			"reset": "リセット",

			"animations": "トランジションを減らす",
			"onScreenControls": "オンスクリーン コントロール",

			"productview": "製品概要",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "前面",
			"back": "背面",
			"left": "左",
			"right": "右",
			"bottom": "下面",
			"top": "上面",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "KO",
			"rotate": "회전",
			"zoom": "확대/축소",
			"move": "이동",						

			"colors": "색상",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "3D로 제품 살펴보기",
			"returnTo3dView": "3D 뷰로 돌아가기",
			"howToUseMenu": "사용 방법",
			"mainmenu": "돌아가기",

			"previousView": "이전 뷰",
			"nextView": "다음 뷰",
			"resetView": "뷰 재설정",

            "previous": "이전",
			"next": "다음",
			"reset": "재설정",

			"animations": "전환 감소",
			"onScreenControls": "On-Screen 제어",

			"productview": "제품 뷰",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "전면",
			"back": "뒤로",
			"left": "Left",
			"right": "Right",
			"bottom": "하단",
			"top": "상단",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "NL",
			"rotate": "Draaien",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Verplaatsen",						

			"colors": "Kleuren",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Product bekijken in 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Terug naar 3D-weergave",
			"howToUseMenu": "Het gebruik",
			"mainmenu": "Hoofdmenu",

			"previousView": "Vorige weergave",
			"nextView": "Volgende weergave",
			"resetView": "Weergave opnieuw instellen",

            "previous": "Vorige",
			"next": "Volgende",
			"reset": "Opnieuw instellen",

			"animations": "Overgangen verminderen",
			"onScreenControls": "Instellingen op het scherm",

			"productview": "Productweergave",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Voorzijde",
			"back": "Terug",
			"left": "Linkerzijde",
			"right": "Rechterzijde",
			"bottom": "onderaan",
			"top": "Boven",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "NO",
			"rotate": "Roter",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Flytt",						

			"colors": "Farger",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Utforsk produktet i 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Gå tilbake til 3D-visning",
			"howToUseMenu": "Brukerveiledning",
			"mainmenu": "Hovedmeny",

			"previousView": "Forrige visning",
			"nextView": "Neste visning",
			"resetView": "Tilbakestill visning",

            "previous": "Forrige",
			"next": "Neste",
			"reset": "Tilbakestill",

			"animations": "Reduser overganger",
			"onScreenControls": "Skjermkontrollere",

			"productview": "Produktvisning",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Foran",
			"back": "Tilbake",
			"left": "Venstre",
			"right": "Høyre",
			"bottom": "Nederst",
			"top": "Topp",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "PL",
			"rotate": "Obrót",
			"zoom": "Powiększenie",
			"move": "Przesuń",						

			"colors": "Kolory",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Obejrzyj produkt w 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Powrót do widoku 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Sposób użycia",
			"mainmenu": "Menu główne",

			"previousView": "Poprzedni widok",
			"nextView": "Następny widok",
			"resetView": "Resetuj widok",

            "previous": "Wstecz",
			"next": "Dalej",
			"reset": "Resetuj",

			"animations": "Ograniczenie liczby zmian",
			"onScreenControls": "Opcje sterowania na ekranie",

			"productview": "Widok produktu",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Przód",
			"back": "Wstecz",
			"left": "Lewa strona",
			"right": "Prawa strona",
			"bottom": "Dół",
			"top": "Góra",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "PT-BR",
			"rotate": "Girar",
			"zoom": "Zoom",
			"move": "Mover",						

			"colors": "Cores",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Explorar produto em 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Voltar à exibição em 3D",
			"howToUseMenu": "Como usar",
			"mainmenu": "Menu principal",

			"previousView": "Exibição anterior",
			"nextView": "Próxima exibição",
			"resetView": "Redefinir exibição",

            "previous": "Anterior",
			"next": "Próxima",
			"reset": "Redefinir",

			"animations": "Reduzir transições",
			"onScreenControls": "Controles na tela",

			"productview": "Exibição do produto",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Parte frontal",
			"back": "Voltar",
			"left": "Esquerda",
			"right": "Direita",
			"bottom": "Inferior",
			"top": "Superior",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
	
		{
			"lang": "SV",
			"rotate": "Rotera",
			"zoom": "Zooma",
			"move": "Flytta",						

			"colors": "Färger",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "Utforska produkten i 3D",
			"returnTo3dView": "Återgå till 3D-vyn",
			"howToUseMenu": "Gör så här",
			"mainmenu": "Huvudmeny",

			"previousView": "Föregående vy",
			"nextView": "Nästa vy",
			"resetView": "Återställ vyn",

            "previous": "Föregåe nde",
			"next": "Nästa",
			"reset": "Återställ",

			"animations": "Minska övergångar",
			"onScreenControls": "Kontroller på skärmen",

			"productview": "Produktöversikt",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "Framsida",
			"back": "Tillbaka",
			"left": "Vänster",
			"right": "Höger",
			"bottom": "Längst ned",
			"top": "Till början",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},

		{
			"lang": "ZH-CN",
			"rotate": "旋转",
			"zoom": "缩放",
			"move": "移动",						

			"colors": "颜色",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "探索产品 3D 模型",
			"returnTo3dView": "返回 3D 视图",
			"howToUseMenu": "使用方式",
			"mainmenu": "主菜单",

			"previousView": "上一视图",
			"nextView": "下一视图",
			"resetView": "重置视图",

            "previous": "上一个",
			"next": "下一个",
			"reset": "重置",

			"animations": "减少过渡",
			"onScreenControls": "屏显控件",

			"productview": "产品图片",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "正面",
			"back": "返回",
			"left": "左侧",
			"right": "右侧",
			"bottom": "底部",
			"top": "顶部",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		},
		{
			"lang": "ZH-TW",
			"rotate": "旋轉",
			"zoom": "縮放",
			"move": "移動",						

			"colors": "色彩",
			"feature": "Accessories",
			
			"exploreProductIn3D": "以 3D 檢視的方式探索產品",
			"returnTo3dView": "返回 3D 檢視",
			"howToUseMenu": "使用方式",
			"mainmenu": "主選單",

			"previousView": "上一個檢視",
			"nextView": "下一個檢視",
			"resetView": "重設檢視",

            "previous": "上一個",
			"next": "下一個",
			"reset": "重設",

			"animations": "減少轉換",
			"onScreenControls": "螢幕控制項",

			"productview": "產品檢視",

			"color1": "Sky",
			"color2": "Slate",

			"front": "前方",
			"back": "返回",
			"left": "左側",
			"right": "右側",
			"bottom": "底部",
			"top": "頂端",
			

			"stylus": "XPS Folio",
			"folio": "XPS Stylus",

			"title": "XPS 13 9315 2in1 SS"
		}
	]
}
